<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Life Update on IT Infrastructure Engineer Labs</title><link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/categories/life-update/</link><description>Recent content in Life Update on IT Infrastructure Engineer Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/categories/life-update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome</title><link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/p/welcome/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/p/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/p/welcome/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Welcome" />&lt;p>Hello Junor IT Infrastructure Engineer! This site&amp;rsquo;s main purpose is to motivate me. I have been really struggling since the end of COVID lockdowns. It has been a long and strange journey. I welcomed my first child, a beautiful and very lively girl. She is wonderful but being a first-time parent is difficult and with all the musings I have lost sight of where I wanted my progression to go. If you are around my age, you probably have a similar story about how you fell in love with technology, so I will not bore you with mine.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now we have all the pleasantries out of the way we can talk about what I want to do here. Simple document my career path forward. Certifications, Home labs and even some leadership/soft skills because the days of the IT staff = basement dwelling trolls are over. Quite frankly this stereo type is overplayed. I am a Junor Network Engineer by trade, but this blog will not be strictly about computer networking. The plan right now is to be ready to take a certification Exam at least every 1.5 yours or so for the next 6 years and use this blog to document it. The primary areas I am going to focus on are Networking, client/server systems and Automation. Now to throw a Rench into the whole ordeal these are going to have to be relatively inexpensive to study for and take because kids are expensive. Also, either closely related to my current job or one I am trying to apply for. I reserve all right to change the criteria whenever I want :laughing: thanks for making this journey with me and see you soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Photo by &lt;a class="link" href="https://unsplash.com/@pawel_czerwinski" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Pawel Czerwinski&lt;/a> on &lt;a class="link" href="https://unsplash.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Unsplash&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>